BUI CONG THANH

Develope

=

Quang Ngai City, Quang Ngai Province

+84 944 32 92 92

congthanhbkit03

w

www.congthanh.edu.vr

SKILL'S

HTML	80%
CSS	70%
JS	90%
JQUERY -	88%
Bootstrap	82%
PHP	85%
PYTHON	7 5%
JAVA	80%
.NET	
LARAVEL	7 5 %

SOCIAL

Facebook cong.thanh.

S S

Skype cong.thanh.58

•

Youtube kienthuctii

Linkedin



ABOUT ME

Web Developer with 5+ years of experience in developing web applications. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle of dynamic web projects.

Quickly learn and master new technologies; successful working in both team and self-directed settings

EXPERIENCE

2007 - 2008

Gameloft - Developer.

Porting- change source code so it can be work in difference mobiles

Fixed bugs

2008 - 2009

FPT Software - Developer.

- Create website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS practices
- Cooperate with web designers to match visual design
- Improved interfaces for existing apps.
- Fixed bugs from existing apps and improved funtionality

2009 - Present

Pham Van Dong University.

Teaching: Web Programming, Programming Language, Python Programming, Scratch

2019 - 2020

ILINXC - Developer.

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intutive interactions and experiences.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and improved web funtionality and speed

2019 - Present

Mentor at Funix University.

Mentoring coures: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, PHP, Laravel, Python

EDUCATION

9 2003 - 2008

Ho Chi Minh City of Technology

Engineer's Degree in Computer Science and Engineering

2011 - 2013

Hue University of Science

Master Degree in Computer Science

PROJECTS

ILINX eForm

Develop a dynamic form system that allows users to create, edit, and submit online forms with dynamic fields. The form should be able to adjust its content based on user actions and previously entered data.

Quang Ngai OCOP Website

Develop a website to support local businesses and households in promoting and selling region-specific products on the OCOP platform. Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Laravel, MySQL.

Quiz Website Development for Pham Van Dong University

Developed a quiz system to support the creation and management of online quizzes for students. The system includes features for question management, quiz creation, automatic grading, and result analysis. The goal of the project is to help teachers easily track and assess student performance, while providing an interactive and convenient learning experience for students. Technologies Used: PHP - jQuery - MySQL

INTEREST

